jntuhaac.in 2018-09-01

# PrivacyPolicy

## Privacy Policy

We value the trust you place in us. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and applicant information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

**1\. PAYMENT SECURITY**

Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

JNTUH AAC website ensures that every transaction that takes between you and our JNTUH AAC website through online is in a safe and secure environment. This can be achieved, as JNTUH AAC website is protected by Secured Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

**2\. COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

We collect personally identifiable information (Email Id., Name, Contact number, etc.) from you when you apply for the JNTUH AAC examination. Any one can browse some sections of our site without being an applicant for JNTUH AAC . Certain do require Registration. We do use your contact information to send you information.

**3\. USE OF DEMOGRAPHIC AND PROFILE DATA**

We use your personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, help promote a safe service, collect fees owed, detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our terms and conditions, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our website. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

**4\. COOKIES**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. JNTUH AAC places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. JNTUH AAC cookies do not contain any of your Personally Identifiable Information.

**5\. SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may share personal information with our other education department and other related department entities and affiliates to help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts, correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services.

We may disclose personal information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy, respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public

**6\. PROHIBITION AGAINST UNLAWFUL USE**

As a condition for the use of the JNTUH AAC Website, the User warrants that they will not use the Website for any purpose that is unlawful or illegal under any law for the time being in force within or outside India or prohibited by this Agreement. In addition, the JNTUH AAC Website shall not be used in any manner, which could damage, disable, overburden or impair it or interfere with any other party's use of the Website. The User shall refrain from obtaining or attempting to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for or through the Website.

**7\. LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

Our site links to other websites that may collect Personally Identifiable Information about you. JNTUH AAC is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

**8\. USE OF COMMUNICATION SERVICES**

JNTUH AAC reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as is necessary to satisfy or comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in JNTUH AAC sole discretion JNTUH AAC does not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any communication service and, therefore, JNTUH AAC specifically disclaims any liability or responsibility whatsoever with regard to the communication services and any actions resulting from the user's participation in any communication service

Materials uploaded to a Communication Service may be subject to posted limitations on usage, reproduction and/or dissemination. User is responsible for keeping himself updated of and adhering to such limitations if they download the materials

JNTUH AAC reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate the access to the website and the related services or any portion thereof at any time, without notice.
